export const sampleQuizList = [
  {
    question: "What is the capital city of Tunisia?",
    options: {
      1: "Tunis",
      2: "Algiers",
      3: "Cairo",
      4: "Rabat",
    },
    correct_answer: "1",
  },
  {
    question: "Which mountain range runs along the northern edge of Tunisia?",
    options: {
      1: "Atlas Mountains",
      2: "Taurus Mountains",
      3: "Aures Mountains",
      4: "Tell Mountains",
    },
    correct_answer: "3",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the largest island off the coast of Tunisia?",
    options: {
      1: "Djerba",
      2: "Sidi Bou Said",
      3: "Monastir",
      4: "Zarzis",
    },
    correct_answer: "1",
  },
  {
    question: "In which year did Tunisia gain independence from France?",
    options: {
      1: "1955",
      2: "1960",
      3: "1947",
      4: "1956",
    },
    correct_answer: "4",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first president of Tunisia after gaining independence?",
    options: {
      1: "Habib Bourguiba",
      2: "Beji Caid Essebsi",
      3: "Moncef Marzouki",
      4: "Kaysar Qalaji",
    },
    correct_answer: "1",
  },
];

export const sampleFlashcardsList = [
  {
    Question: "What is the capital city of Tunisia?",
    Answer: "Tunis",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which language is the official language of Tunisia?",
    Answer: "Arabic (official), French and Italian are also widely spoken",
  },
  {
    Question: "Who was the leader that led Tunisia to independence in 1956?",
    Answer: "Habib Bourguiba",
  },
  {
    Question:
      "What is the name of the largest island off the coast of Tunisia?",
    Answer: "Djerba Island",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which mountain range runs along the north of Tunisia?",
    Answer: "Atlas Mountains",
  },
];
